The target has appeared.
Are you sure he's alone?
Yes.
Mr. Wen is meeting
with some veterans
in the VIP room with Liu Yaru.
He won't be in the main hall
for at least ten minutes.
The show begins.
Actually,
life is like snooker.
Mistake
is the best offense.
Mr. Lin,
have a good sleep.
I'm actually quite tired.
I feel like a marionette.
Marriage,
getting promoted,
maintaining the status quo,
Every step has been planned out.
Even taking full control
has to wait until after marriage.
That's my dad's decision.
Then Liu Yaru
is indeed a good choice.
She...
Don't mention her.
I don't feel it at all.
I don't want
to be manipulated.
Manipulated?
I thought people like you
were born in Rome.
Rome?
Rome was built by someone else.
My mom
has been too strict with me since I was young.
I'm tired.
What I need now
is someone who can help me
take over the company as soon as possible,
not a wife
who just listens to me.
Oh,
what kind of wife do you want?
Smart,
skilled,
and not a burden.
So,
you don't want a wife,
but a partner.
Yes.
A partner who can help each other.
Then why don't you consider me?
You're quite direct.
Since we're all about taking what we need,
being direct isn't a bad thing, is it?
I have a way
to help you stabilize the situation
and take control.
And all I want is to be your wife.
I won't ask for your premarital property.
I'll just take what I deserve.
After you're in power,
I'll take my money and leave.
And you
can continue to be the CEO.
How about that?
So this is your real purpose
of getting close to me?
People die for wealth,
and birds die for food.
What's wrong with that?
But,
I was just kidding.
I'm drunk,
so I talk nonsense.
Don't mind it.
But,
if you take it seriously,
I'm always ready.
[Guan Tiantian,]
[who are you really?]
Bai Qiang.
Enough, Mr. Zhao.
Stop glaring.
If it weren't for Mr. Lin's order,
I wouldn't bother with your mess.
Take a look.
If there are no objections,
sign the settlement agreement.
You're so cruel
to ask for so much.
That's what you deserve.
It's pointless to argue.
Mr. Zhao,
you're a smart man.
You should know what to choose.
Fine.
I'll accept it this time.
Mr. Guan,
thank you so much
for helping me get this far.
Let me treat you to a big meal.
I also want to thank you
for helping me solve a big problem.
This kind of good thing
should happen more often.
With this money,
I can finally catch my breath
and start over.
Don't dance on the edge of a knife.
Be careful not to hurt yourself.
It's better to stay away
from people like Zhao Zhiwei.
I know, Guan Lu.
But
you're right.
Women
can't always wait to be bullied.
I was
too weak and too stupid before.
But not anymore.
That's why
I'm here to learn.
Learn?
Here?
Yes.
My friend recommended this place.
She said it could teach us
how to meet people
of a higher class,
how to protect ourselves,
and how to use the rules
to get what we want.
I don't want to be that Bai Qiang anymore,
who just gets beaten up
and waits for someone else to save her.
I want to be like you,
both beautiful
and strong,
playing those self-righteous men
like a fiddle.
Excuse me,
sorry to interrupt.
You go in first.
I'll have a word with this lady.
May I ask,
do you know this person?
No, I don't.
Then,
do you have any impression
of the name Wang Jiming?
I'm sorry, ma'am,
I don't know anyone you mentioned.
You are Xiaoyu, right?
I'm sorry.
If you keep bothering me,
I'll call the police.
Zhao Zhiwei's matter has been resolved.
His project
can continue to be promoted.
This Guan Lu
is quite capable.
Jiming,
you've found a good helper.
Bro,
you haven't heard that
Guan Lu is more effective
than some vice presidents
in the company now.
There is a problem with the flow of funds.
The relevant materials are here.
Director Liu, you can have a look.
What do you mean, Lin Jiming?
Are you trying to frame me?
I'm not against you.
You need to
explain the whole thing.
Well,
bro,
calm down.
Jiming
is just doing his job.
Maybe
it's Guan Yu's way
of making a name
for himself
in the new position.
It's just business.
Please understand.
Liu Yaru,
the handover of the audit department
hasn't been completed yet.
You're already starting to care
about the specific business.
It's just a matter of time.
I just don't want to be like someone,
using the name of work
to get rid of rivals.
Auntie Wen.
Director Wen.
Mom.
Yaru,
you go out for a while.
OK.
Ah.
You can't hold your temper for a little thing.
What a shame!
Jiming
Come out.
Our Lin Group has a solid foundation
for so many years.
Do you know why we have to
go public now?
You said
this is to help me take over the company
and complete the power transition.
That's right.
The key is,
during the process of going public,
we should get rid of
all the obstacles,
and hold on
to all the things
we should hold.
But,
you were too hasty.
Why did you have to go after Liu Yaping?
He's the biggest obstacle.
Ever since he inherited his father's shares,
he's been targeting me.
Keeping him around
means I can't truly take control.
You're still so impatient.
Hitting without killing
is the way to control people.
If Liu Yaping falls,
his faction
will be like a headless fly,
running around wildly,
which will be more troublesome.
Keeping him in this position
is the only way to make his faction
obey.
You must make it realistic.
Understood, Chairman Liu.
So I have to endure it all,
even if he hinders me at every turn
and treats me like a puppet.
I must follow every step you've set.
That's right.
I personally
paved the way for you.
You don't have the luxury to make mistakes.
Messing with the Liu family
is a wrong move.
The Liu family can provide you with
the auditing endorsement and network you need.
Such a marriage
is what has value.
Keeping Liu Yaru on board
is your only
correct choice now.
Mom,
I've said I don't like it.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
Guan Law Firm is really everywhere.
You just finished stirring up trouble with my brother,
and now you're in a hurry to go up
and show off to Jiming.
You're really efficient.
I solve problems for the company,
so I naturally appear where needed.
Unlike some people
who only know how to create problems.
Create problems?
Guan Liangliang,
you're the one who sowed discord in front of my brother,
hinting at his unclear accounts.
You call this solving problems?
This is clearly
stirring up trouble and muddying the waters.
Data is objective.
If Mr. Liu feels offended,
he should reflect on the process itself,
not question the person who uncovered the issue.
Or,
do you also think
the flow of that fund
is questionable?
You...
Guan Tiantian,
stop pretending to be so noble in front of me.
Don't think
I don't know your plans.
You want to climb up by stepping on us,
and take over
my position.
You wish!
Your position?
Ms Liu,
I think you
haven't figured out the situation.
There was never a position for you.
How could you be replaced?
You should know Mr. Lin's thoughts
better than I do.
You...
This isn't the place for you to act up.
Ms. Liu,
mind your manners.
Instead of venting your frustration on me,
you'd better think about
how to help your brother
wipe his ass clean.
It's time to get rid of the dirt.
Guan Tiantian,
I won't let you off the hook.
I heard
the new legal counsel
found a problem with the company's funds.
Yes.
She is
exceptionally capable.
I don't care if she's truly talented
or has ulterior motives.
you can only play around with her,
don't fall in love with her,
and don't let her
break the rules.
The position of Mrs. Lin
is not something
a woman of unknown background
can covet.
Follow my plan,
get married smoothly,
and completely stabilize the situation.
Then,
I can
fully
entrust
the Lin Group to you.
Don't let me think
you're not up to the task.
Liu Yaping's
abnormal fund flow,
just put it on hold for now.
Why?
No reason.
Just do it.
You're the boss,
of course, you have the final say.
But could you also tell me
why
we should let go of such a good opportunity?
There are some things
I have my reasons for.
Just do as I say,
okay?
Okay.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Tomorrow's the weekend,
why don't we
go relax?
Is this considered
a date between a boss and employee?
You can think of it
team building.
Team building.
Okay.
Where do you want to go?
How about horse riding on the beach?
Mr. Guan,
this is for you.
Your flowers.
Oh.
Thank you.
I'll go now.
See you this weekend.